Next, let's take a look at how to modify this dress hat into a women's woolen hat
First, we first delete the excess fake stitches, and then simulate by pressing the control key
After we have all the disassembly and simulation, let's freeze the hat first
Let's modify this top plate first
Because we want to make it into a round hat top, we first select the round plate
Then activate the center point and drag the frame to form a smaller circle
After forming a smaller circle, we need to adjust this side
First, we need to calculate its length
You can see it in the attribute editor
Then use the change length tool to modify the length of this side to match the length of this small plate
After the modification, it is the same as when we made the magician hat
We need to adjust this curve so that the corresponding position of the side seam can form a state close to the right angle
After completion, we will start to simulate
Let it simulate
After the simulation, we need to use the tool to edit the curve point
Continue to adjust the curve of the bottom and top side
Change it to a side that can be close to the right angle effect
TWные procedure
Saw off the settled creases
Next, because we want to shorten the height
So now we need to select the peak on the top
Cap Fit
After cutting, we can delete the excess part and re-create the sewing line
After sewing, because we re-create the sewing line, the folding angle of the sewing line returns to 180
So now it will be a round top
What we are going to do next is to adjust the width of the side of this board
Let it be more narrow
In order to match the length of the round top, we need to modify its length
In addition to adjusting the round top, we can also press the Ctrl key to slide along the side of the diagonal to form a right angle
Because the curve will affect our adjustment, we can delete the excess curve first
Only keep some of the middle parts
Like this
After finishing the simulation, some跑 may not be good
In the strange move, we still need to modify the design
First, we continue to adjust the angle along the side, to adjust the other side
After the top two corners are close to 90 degrees
We can turn it over and increase or decrease the angle after we finish the Carry-On like this
you can use this curve as a reference to adjust the curve of the bottom
In the process of adjustment, if there is a part of the area that is a little bit wider
we can continue to adjust the curve
If you think the width on the side is a little short
we can lengthen the straight line in the back middle alone
And then we can simulate the smoke and fire
so that they can be simulated together
Then we can add the butterfly knot
In our library window
we can see Hardware and Trims
Some of the files here are some of our accessories
We can find the Ribbon file
If it's empty here
we can click the download button in the upper right corner
In addition to being able to download the whole thing
we can also download a specific object separately
If its selection box is gray
we can click this little arrow to download it
Here we double click this butterfly knot file
and add it to the work area
The position is selected as the original position
and the position is selected as the original position
After we have added it
we can select the water glue tool in the upper right corner of the positioning ball
and then click this hat plate
and we can stick the butterfly knot on top of the hat
Then click the deformation tool in the upper right corner
and we can drag the axis on the positioning ball
to be loosened
and then we can drag the axis on the position of the butterfly knot
Next, if we want to do the bag effect
we can directly select the bottom side of this side
and then right click to draw a line along the inner line of it
Then cut this line off
and then we can drag this line along the inner line of the butterfly knot
If it's just the texture surface
then our board is not thick
It only shows the front and back
After cutting, we can switch to the thick texture surface
Only when the display type is the thick texture surface
can the thickness of the board really be displayed in the 3D window
Then switch to the thick texture surface
We want to increase the thickness of the board
After increasing the thickness of the board
The board is in a state with thickness
Then it looks like there is a layer of tape outside
Here we can also open the double layer display
After opening the double layer display
The side of the board looks like it has a two-layer structure
We can also use the foldable angle to find the foldable angle
This is a spatial angle
If you look at this foldable angle
In order to easily identify the tape and the hat body
We can copy a fabric
And apply this fabric to the tape
Finally, we can re-set the angle of folding between the fern string
Let this hat have a down angle that covers the着 羊 帽
Because of our fold angle calculation
The lower the angle, that is, the closer it is to 180 degrees, the flatter the angle of the two panels
So we want to reduce its folding angle from 270 to 240
Finally, we adjust the position of the butterfly knot
Select a
We can set its intensity to 0 on the 3D fountain line on the right, so that there is no effect of the fountain line at the joint
As for the thickness, it is actually the depth and thickness of the fountain line
The higher we raise this value, the more obvious the effect of the fountain line will be
Here, you can set it to 0